{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "1. Which of the following is a correct statement?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "PI Controllers improve steady state response",
        "b": "PD controllers improve transient response",
        "c": "All of the above",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "2. What is the relation between gain (g) and proportional band (p) in control system",
      "answers": {
        "a": " g = 100/p",
        "b": "g = p",
        "c": "g = p/100",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "3. Which of the following is an example of actuator?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Microphone",
        "b": "Solenoid",
        "c": "Micro switch",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "4. What is magnetic levitation?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "The use of magnetic fields to cause a train to rise above the rails",
        "b": "The use of fields to stretch a train above the rails",
        "c": "To use of fields to shrink a train above the rails",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "5. A disadvantage of implementing MAGLEV systems is, it can be",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Not safe",
        "b": "Not environmental friendly",
        "c": "Costly",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	{
      "question": "6. Increasing the proportional gain in PID block will __________ the rise time",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Increase",
        "b": "Not affect",
        "c": "Decrease",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },	
	
	{
      "question": "7. A proportional band setting of 175% is equivalent to a gain setting of __",
      "answers": {
        "a": "175",
        "b": "0.756",
        "c": "0.571",
        "d": "1.32"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	{
      "question": "8. Which one of the following controllers increases the order of the system by one? ",
      "answers": {
        "a": "P controller",
        "b": "PI controller",
        "c": "Both the above",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	
	{
      "question": "9. The magnetic levitation is __________ ",
      "answers": {
        "a": "A non contact technology",
        "b": "Not a non contact technology",
        "c": "Both of the above",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
	
	{
      "question": "10. Strength of an electromagnet can be increased by",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Increasing the cross-sectional area",
        "b": "Increasing the number of turns",
		"c": "Increasing current supply",
        "d": "All of the above"
		
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
	
  ]
}
